nonags.com 2016-01-05

# NONAGS.COM. Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement for NONAGS.COM**

NONAGS.COM. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: **NONAGS.COM** , is operated by NONAGS.COM Ltd., located in Tewksbury, MA, USA. 

Your IP address is used only when you become a member as a backup identification tool for polls and other member services. Or as identification tool when you post messages in our forums. 

Our site may use cookies to store information about your membership, and the content contained is not distributed to third parties. 

* * *

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

* * *

This site contains links to other sites. **NONAGS.COM** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online forms may ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. We do not share this information with third parties. 

**Public Forums** Our site has forums, and message boards, available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. **Security** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true. **Children's Guidelines** This site gives children under the age of 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. **Contacting the Web Site:**   [_Contacts Link_](http://www.nonags.com/mail.asp)
